Elizabeth Finlon

Contact

Objective

715 Oakland Ave., Oakland, CA 94611 404 906 3195 efinlon1@gmail.com Holds a Master of Public Health degree in Environmental Health and a B.I.S. degree in Environmental Science, both from Georgia State University. Has significant experience in both data- and statistical analysis as well as objectoriented programming.

Key Skills

Education

Python (NumPy, Pandas, scikit-learn) SQL Java **JavaScript RStudio** Data Visualization (Seaborn, Matplotlib)

Cook Systems FastTrack Java Program Memphis, TN Concentrated Java Frameworks and Developer Tools Training May 2021

UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN Python for Everybody Specialization December 2020

GEORGIA STATE UNIVERSITY

Atlanta, GA

Master of Public Health

May 2018

- Graduate Research Assistantship
- GPA 3.85

GEORGIA STATE UNIVERSITY

Atlanta, GA

Bachelor of Interdisciplinary Studies

December 2012

- **Environmental Science**
- GPA 3.91; Summa Cum Laude; Departmental Distinctions

References

HTML/CSS

Experience

Available upon request.

Cook Systems, Inc. Software Developer

Memphis, TN May 2021-Present

Highwire Coffee Roasters Educational Director

Berkeley, CA

August 2019-February 2021

- Created/implemented employee education protocol
- Performed company-wide QA/QC
- Facilitated hiring & onboarding of new employees

Utilized extensive customer service experience in day-to-day workflow

Georgia State University

Atlanta, GA

Graduate Research Assistant August 2015-August 2017

- Implemented R, Python, SAS, & Excel-based data analytics
- Performed meta-analyses for peer-reviewed publications
- Conducted lab analyses & designed data-collection procedures
- Trained volunteers in data collection

Environmental Protection Agency

Atlanta, GA

Intern, Superfund Division, Scientific Support Section January 2017-June 2017

- Calculated risk assessments for federal reports
- Drafted copy to communicate health risks with public
- Maintained databases of multiple federal Superfund sites
- Managed data & spreadsheets for multi-departmental projects